{"data":[{"question":"I saw a sample ________ her work and it was quite impressed.","a":"of","b":"in","c":"on","d":"about","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sample of sth = an example of something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The U.S. postal service policy for check approval includes a requirement that two pieces of identification ________.","a":"must present","b":"presented","c":"be presented","d":"for presentation","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + S + Infinitive (without to) + O.\u00a0\n- Passive voice: Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + BE +PP- Adverb modifies.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Nerve impulses ________ to the brain at a speed of about one hundred yards per second.","a":"sending sensations","b":"to send sensations","c":"send sensations","d":"be send sensations","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Although exact statistics vary because of political changes, ________ separate nation states are included in the official lists at any one time.","a":"more than two hundred","b":"as much as two hundred","c":"many as two hundred","d":"most that two hundred","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Comparison of Equality: as + adj\/ adv+ as.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"________ owe much of their success as a group to their unusual powers of migration.","a":"That birds","b":"A bird","c":"The bird","d":"Birds","answer":"4","explain":"\n - That birds: it's a clause not a sentence.\u00a0\n- A bird\/the bird- owes.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I believe ________ things openly.","a":"of discussing","b":"for discussing","c":"in discussing","d":"on discussing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Believe in somebody or something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Research in the work place reveals that people work for many reasons ________.","a":"money beside","b":"money besides","c":"beside money","d":"besides money","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Besides: means \"in addition to\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Seals can ________ because they have a thick layer of blubber under their fur.","a":"keep them warm","b":"keep themselves warm","c":"they keep warm","d":"keep their warm","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Keep sbd\/sth + adj.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Both liquids and gases flow freely from a container because they have ________.","a":"not definite shape","b":"none definite shape","c":"nothing definite shape","d":"no definite shape","answer":"4","explain":"- No: used as a determiner followed by a noun (means not any)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"One of Shaw's ________, \"Pygmalion\", was the story that formed the basis for the musical play \"my fair lady\".","a":"greatest work","b":"greatest works","c":"the greatest work","d":"the greatest works","answer":"2","explain":"\n- One of + plural noun.\u00a0\n- The greatest + singular noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}